import { Question } from "../contestantControls";

export const mattQuestions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 61,
    question: "What is Ekko’s ultimate name?",
    options: ["Duplicate", "Replicate", "copy"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 62,
    question: "How many overwatch 2 heroes can fly (not jump)?",
    options: ["3", "5", "7"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 63,
    question: "What is Tracer’s recall (E) cooldown?",
    options: ["15s", "12s", "10s"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 64,
    question: "How many overwatch 2 heroes cant headshot?",
    options: ["7", "4", "9"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 65,
    question: "What gamemode was removed in overwatch 2?",
    options: ["Push", "Hybrid", "Two control Point"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 66,
    question: "How much healing per second does zenyatta’s ultimate heal?",
    options: ["700", "400", "1500"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 67,
    question: "What time is referred to in a famous overwatch ultimate voice line?",
    options: ["Dinner time", "12pm", "Sundown"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 68,
    question: "What category of heroes has the fewest members?",
    options: ["Support", "Tank", "Damage"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 69,
    question: "What is the name of the gamemode creator within the overwatch game engine?",
    options: ["Workshop", "Custom", "Sandbox"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 70,
    question: "Widowmaker’s ballet skins, Odette and Odile, come from what famous ballet?",
    options: ["Swan lake", "The nutcracker", "Giselle"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 71,
    question: "Other than keeping their original skins/unlocks, what did overwatch 2 players who owned overwatch receive for free?",
    options: ["Free battle pass", "Kiriko", "Legacy player icon"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 72,
    question: "What does GOATS in the context of the infamous triple tank, triple support meta stand for?",
    options: ["GO All Tanks and Supports", "Guardians Of Ambition, Tenacity, and Strength", "Greatest Of All Time(S)"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 73,
    question: "What’s the name of the latest character to have a hero trial period in Overwatch 2?",
    options: ["Bulwark", "Wuyang", "Ashura"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 74,
    question: "When was Overwatch 2 officially released?",
    options: ["November 2022", "August 2023", "June 2023"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 75,
    question: "How many damage type heroes are in Overwatch 2?",
    options: ["21", "24", "19"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  }
];